herbalbiz.com 2019-05-27

# 

## Privacy Policy

Last Updated on May 25, 2018 

We (and our affiliates) are committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy applies to all our websites ("Websites") and our services ("Service").

This Privacy Policy governs our data collection, processing and usage practices. It also describes your choices regarding use, access and correction of your personal information. If you do not agree with the data practices described in this Privacy Policy, you should not use the Websites or the Service.

We periodically update this Privacy Policy. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice by sending you an email notification.

While we will notify you of any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we encourage you to review this Privacy Policy periodically.

  1. Information we collect about you
  2. How and why we use your personal data
  3. How we use your personal data for marketing
  4. How we share your data with third parties
  5. How we protect your data
  6. How long we keep your personal data
  7. Your rights
  8. Contact us
  9. Cookies

#### 1\. Information we collect about you

Personal and contact information including your name, age, telephone number, postal address, email address, username and social media username(s). We may collect some of that contact information when you interact with us including via our Customer Care Team.

Details (and copies) of your communications and interactions with us via our Customer Care Team or otherwise, including by email, telephone (voice recordings), post and online via webchat, the feedback button or on social media channels.

Copies of documents you provide to prove your identity (including driving license and passport) when there is a legal reason to request this from you.

Transaction details including payments from you for subscription or purchase of the Service.

Your financial information including your payment card information when you make a purchase or subscribe to the Service.

Information about how you use our Websites, and which websites you came to us from.

Technical information about your device or browser when you use our Websites, including geolocation data to determine what country you are accessing our Websites from, your internet protocol (IP) address, device ID, browser type and version and time zone setting, which may in some circumstances be personal data.

We may also receive personal data directly from you or from various third parties and public sources, including from social media channels (if you interact with us through those channels), or other third parties.

#### 2\. How and why we use your personal data

Below, we set out all of the ways we use your personal data, and why. We have also identified what our legitimate interests are where appropriate. 

It is sometimes necessary for us to process your personal data in order to enter into a contract with you, or to satisfy a contractual requirement (referred to as "performance of a contract with you" below), or to comply with a statutory requirement. In those circumstances, if you do not provide the personal data we require, we will be unable to provide our services to you. 

_Registration_

How:| We use your personal and contact information to register you as a new customer/client. We collect financial information if you register payment card information when purchasing or subscribing to one of our services.  
---|---  
Why:| Necessary for the performance of a contract with you.  
  
_Accessing Website content_

How:| We use the personal and contact information provided by you and the transaction details about your purchases, to provide our services to you.  
---|---  
Why:| Necessary for the performance of a contract with you.  
  
_Managing your account_

How:| We use your personal and contact information, financial information, and transaction details about your purchases, to manage your account.  
---|---  
Why:| Necessary for the performance of a contract with you.  
  
_Communicating with you_

How:| We use the personal and contact information provided by you, copies of your communications with us and, in some circumstances, transaction details, to manage our relationship with you. For example: 

  * to notify you about changes to our Account Terms or Privacy Policy;
  * to communicate with you in response to any query, request or complaint you may have including by email, telephone and in web chat whether relating to any services that you have purchased from us or otherwise.

---|---  
Why:| Necessary for the performance of a contract with you.  
Necessary to comply with a legal obligation.  
Necessary for our legitimate interests (to keep our records updated and to study the services we provide).  
  
_Staff training_

How:| We may use copies of your communications with us (including voice recordings) in order to train our staff.  
---|---  
Why:| Necessary for our legitimate interests (to ensure that we are able to provide the best service to you).  
  
_Market research_

How:| We may use the personal and contact information you have provided to ask you to take part in market research or a survey. We also use the results of any surveys or market research that you undertake to improve our Websites and services.  
---|---  
Why:| Necessary for our legitimate interests (to assess and improve our services and business).  
  
_Technical issues_

How:| If you contact us about an issue, we may use technical information, and personal and contact information to administer and protect our business and Website (including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, system maintenance, support, reporting and hosting of data).  
---|---  
Why:| Necessary for our legitimate interests (for providing our services, the provision of administration and IT services, security and fraud prevention). Necessary to comply with a legal obligation.  
  
_Experience_

How:| We use information about your use of our Websites, together with technical information about your device and (in some circumstances) your personal and contact information, and other relevant information that we receive from you or third parties (including aggregated information that we combine with your personal data), to deliver relevant website content and other marketing to you, and to manage the delivery of that content. For example, we may automatically display relevant advertisements to you based on your use of our Websites.  
---|---  
Why:| Necessary for our legitimate interests (to ensure that you are shown relevant content based on your use of our Websites).  
  
_Advertising effectiveness_

How:| We use information about your use of our Websites and, in some circumstances, personal and contact information about you, to measure or understand the effectiveness of the advertising we serve to you.  
---|---  
Why:| Necessary for our legitimate interests (to determine how effective advertising is in order to improve advertising, its relevance and in order to fulfil contracts we have with our marketing partners).  
  
_Analytics_

How:| We use information about your use of our Websites and technical information, including about your device or where you are accessing our Websites from, to optimize our service and to improve our app, Website, services, direct marketing, student relationships, behavior profiling and experiences.  
---|---  
Why:| Necessary for our legitimate interests (to measure the interactions with our Websites, to keep our Websites updated and relevant, to develop our business and to improve our marketing strategy).  
  
_Publicity_

How:| We may use your personal and limited contact information in any publicity materials provided that you have given your consent.   
---|---  
Why:| Necessary for our legitimate interests (to develop our business and to improve our marketing strategy).  
  
_Regulatory compliance_

How:| We may use your personal and contact information, financial information, information about any transaction between you and us, information about your use of our Websites, or technical information, to enable us to comply with our legal and regulatory obligations.  
---|---  
Why:| Necessary to comply with a legal obligation.  
  
_Fraud prevention_

How:| We may use your personal and contact information, financial information, information about any transaction between you and us, information about your use of our Websites, or technical information, in order to undertake analysis for the purposes of identifying and dealing with any fraud or fraudulent activity.  
---|---  
Why:| Necessary to comply with a legal obligation. Necessary for our legitimate interests (to ensure that transactions and interactions with us are not fraudulent).  
  
_Queries_

How:| We may use your personal and contact information, financial information, information about any transaction between you and us, information about your use of our Websites, or technical information for the purpose of dealing with any request, complaint or query from you.  
---|---  
Why:|  Necessary to comply with a legal obligation. Necessary for our legitimate interests (to respond to you and to deal with any request you may have).  
  
We use your personal data to create aggregated data sets. You are not identifiable from that aggregated data and it is not considered personal data.

However, if we combine or connect aggregated data with your personal data so that it can directly or indirectly identify you, we treat the combined data as personal data which will be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

#### 3\. How we use your personal data for marketing

We send you marketing communications through a number of different channels. You may receive newsletters, email notifications and other marketing communications that either you request from us or which you consent to by opting in when completing a registration form on our service., and/or have not asked us to stop sending marketing by email to you.

How to opt out of this marketing

You may opt out from receiving such marketing communications and notifications from us at any time. There are several ways you can do this. To stop receiving marketing by email, either:

  * Click "unsubscribe" or update preferences in any email communication we send;
  * Contact us in writing; or
  * Email us at domainadmincontact@gmail.com.

#### 4\. How we share your data with third parties

We sometimes share the data we collect from you with the following trusted third parties:

  * Banks and payment providers - to set up and/or to obtain payment of any amounts due to us.
  * Our IT system providers - in order to provide software to set up your account, to communicate with you via webchat and other communications providers and to provide our systems to us, including for the purposes of hosting, support and software licensing.
  * Social media platforms - for the purpose of fulfilling the service and targeted advertising.
  * Online survey companies and market research agencies - to undertake surveys (including for example, our Websites satisfaction survey) and other market research and to analyze the results.
  * Digital analytics companies - for the purposes of website analytics and reporting in respect of our analytics and marketing.
  * Professional advisers including lawyers, bankers, auditors and insurers - for the purposes of providing consultancy, banking, legal, insurance and accounting services.
  * Police or other such regulatory authority - as part of an investigation or otherwise for legal or regulatory purposes.
  * Auditors - to audit our systems and transactions for the purposes of ensuring efficiency, or regulatory or contractual compliance.
  * We will disclose your personal information to third parties if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal or regulatory obligation or request. We do this in order to protect our rights, property or safety or of our clients, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection.

How to opt out of this marketing

You may opt out from receiving such marketing communications and notifications from us at any time. There are several ways you can do this. To stop receiving marketing by email, either:

  * Click "unsubscribe" or update preferences in any email communication we send;
  * Contact us in writing; or
  * Email us at domainadmincontact@gmail.com.

#### 5\. How we protect your data

We have put various measures in place to protect your personal data:

  * All of your shopping cart checkout information is processed on our secure servers. You can see this via the https:// in the url as well as your browser showing the site listed as "Secure" in the address bar. This means that all of the data is encrypted while it is being transmitted for security purposes.
  * When your data is received and processed, it is stored on secured servers with restricted access with all necessary and reasonable safeguards put in place to protect said information.
  * In some cases, we may disclose your personal data to third parties. If and when we do so, we make every effort to ensure the third party takes all necessary steps to secure the information and protect your data. However, in some cases we may be required by law to disclose your information to a third party and may not always have control over how that information is secured.
  * Your personal data may be processed by our staff or one of the referenced third parties. At such times only the minimum amount of data needed to perform their given duties is accessed. Such staff may exist outside of the EEA (European Economic Area.)

#### 6\. How long we keep your personal data

We will only keep your personal data for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements.

At the end of that retention period, your data will either be deleted or anonymized (so that it can no longer be associated with you) for research or statistical purposes.

To determine the appropriate retention period for personal data, we consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the personal data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorized use or disclosure of your personal data, the purposes for which we process your personal data and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal requirements.

In some circumstances, you may be entitled to ask us to delete your data: see "Your rights" below for further information.

#### 7\. Your rights

You have the right:

  * to ask us not to use your personal data for marketing;
  * to ask us not to process your personal data where it is processed on the basis of legitimate interests, if there are no compelling reasons for that processing;
  * to request from us access to personal information held about you (see below);
  * to ask for the information we hold about you to be rectified if it is inaccurate or incomplete;
  * to ask that we stop any consent-based processing of your personal data after you withdraw that consent;
  * to ask, in certain circumstances, to delete the personal data we hold about you;
  * to ask, in certain circumstances, for the processing of that information to be restricted; and
  * to ask, in certain circumstances, for data portability.

#### 8\. Contact us

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, including any requests to exercise your rights, please contact the Data Protection Officer at domainadmincontact@gmail.com.

In order to request a copy of the personal data that we hold about you, please send your request in writing to the Data Protection Officer at the above address. To enable us to verify your identity and process your request, you must include all of the following information and documentation with your request:

  * your full name;
  * the email address registered to your account;
  * a description of the data that you are requesting, including a date range;
  * proof of your ID;
  * the date of the request.

If you are unhappy with our processing of your personal data, you have the right to complain at any time. We would, however, appreciate the chance to deal with any concerns before you approach the appropriate authority, so please contact the Data Protection Officer by email in the first instance.

#### 9\. Cookies

We use cookies and similar technologies to recognize you, your browser and your device. We also allow carefully selected third parties to use cookies, pixels and ad tags while you are browsing our Websites. These collect information about your browsing habits and usage and allow us to show you ads while you are browsing our Websites and other sites on the internet. All of our advertising cookies used are described in the cookie list below.

There are four main types of cookies and technology. Here's how and why we use them:

_Strictly necessary cookies_

These are cookies that are required for the operation of our Websites. Without these cookies, you will not be able to use some functionality on our Websites, such as signing into your account.

_Performance cookies_

These cookies collect information about how you use our Websites and help us improve the way our Websites work by making it easier for you to navigate to and complete various tasks.

_Functionality cookies_

These cookies allow us to identify whether you are logged into your Figure Eight Training portal and to remember choices you make and your preferences, in order to improve your experience of our Websites.

_Advertising cookies and pixels_

Our carefully selected media partners place third party cookies, pixels and ad tags onto our Websites on our behalf. These cookies record your visit to our Websites, the pages you have visited and the links you have followed.

We use this information to make our Websites, and the content displayed on them, more relevant to you. They are also used to limit the number of times you see certain content, as well to measure the effectiveness of our digital campaigns.

We may share this analytics information with third parties for these purposes. You can delete these cookies and still continue to use our Websites.

More information about these types of cookies and opt out information can be found in Manage your cookies.

_Managing your cookies_

For more information about cookies, how to opt out and the steps you can take to protect your privacy on the internet, go tohttp://www.youronlinechoices.com- the guide to online behavioral advertising and privacy. This website is operated by the Internet Advertising Bureau, the industry body for online advertising. On here you'll find information about how behavioral advertising works, how to opt out, further information about cookies and the steps you can take to protect your privacy on the internet.

If you'd prefer to restrict, block or delete cookies from our Websites, you can do so in your browser settings. If you choose to disable cookies, then please note that this may limit the way you use our Websites. For example, you may have to re-enter information that would have ordinarily been stored as a cookie.

_How to control cookies on your desktop_

_How to control cookies on your mobile device_

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Any changes that we may make to our Privacy Policy in the future will be posted on our Websites. Where appropriate, we will notify you of the changes periodically.

Copyright 2018 | Last Updated on May 25, 2018 | All Rights Reserved
